wisconsingazette.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Site | wisconsingazette.com

Wisconsin Gazette, (WiG), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Wisconsin Gazette of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.           

 ** _THEREFORE_** , this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Wisconsin Gazette, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of wisconsingazette.com you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.

 **Collection of Information**

It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.

 **Use of Information Collected**

Wisconsin Gazette may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from wisconsingazette.com . Wisconsin Gazette  may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.

Wisconsin Gazette may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

  * Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Wisconsin Gazette and/or our website;
  * Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Wisconsin Gazette; and
  * Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of wisconsingazette.com and/or the general public.

Advertisers and third parties also may collect information about your activity on our site and applications, on devices associated with you, and on third-party sites and applications using tracking technologies. Tracking data collected by these advertisers and third parties is used to decide which ads you see both on our sites and applications and on third-party sites and applications, but does not identify you personally and is not associated with your registration account. You may [choose not to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks,](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) data exchanges, marketing analytics and other service providers. You may also choose to control targeted advertising you receive within applications by using your mobile device settings (for example, by re-setting your device's advertising identifier and/or opting out of interest based ads). We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.

 **Unsubscribe or Opt-Out**

All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to . If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.

 **Links to Other Web Sites**

Our website does contain links to other websites. Wisconsin Gazette does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.

 **Security**

Wisconsin Gazette shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under our control.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement**

Wisconsin Gazette reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at wisconsingazette.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Wisconsin Gazette decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.

 **Acceptance of Terms**

Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.

 **Email:** [news@wisconsingazette.com](mailto:news@wisconsingazette.com)

 **Telephone Number:** 414-961-3240

 **Mailing Address:**

      Wisconsin Gazette

      3956 N Murray Ave.

      Shorewood, Wisconsin 53211

Effective: June 7, 2018
